[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", ":", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What is your view of the new Pope, the Catholic Church as it stands, and what the challenge is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, we're just figuring him out and part of it I love already, his commitment to the poor and his own -- avoiding the trappings of the very, very wealthy cardinals that we see sort of displaying their regalia but the other part of him that is so biased against marriage equality and intolerant, that's the part of the church that I feel that if everyone isn't welcome, it's very -- it's as if I was going to a country club and they said well, this person can't come because they are black or because they are Jewish or because they are gay.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Francis"]}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "But what do you think the new Pope needs to do to slightly move with the times without alienating perhaps the traditions of the church?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I think he took a very important first step by choosing the name Francis.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How are you going to get a more modern Catholic Church and in fact how are you going to deal with religion amongst young people generally of any type of religion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "You mentioned world Catholics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mia"]}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What was it that got you back into being a devout Catholic again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, I had a similar experience as Mia had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What do you make of what is going on at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I think they're really cowardly because they know in their hearts that there's no need -- we're talking about assault weapons here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Why do you think so few politicians are taking what I would see to be a courageous moral lead on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, what's new.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "How do you change the debate around children and in particular with guns, particularly following what happened at Newtown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "It is horrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "They're stadium events.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "How is she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "She's doing OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "NN", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I think this really exposes a problem that we have in America and probably worldwide, almost, with children and parents as to knowing what our parents are doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "So you just grabbed her and that was a fun picture that you took?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, after that, I didn't think it was fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "In the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "It was a joke picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What did you think when you read that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I just texted him like what are you talking about, you're playing; stop playing with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "That it was a silly prank, it got completely out of hand, and when these kids all woke up the next day, they all had bitter regret about what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I guess anything is possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["next day"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Are they brought up to be disrespectful to women, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What does it tell us about modern young America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, I think what's important is what the prosecutor said today, which was that it's really about degradation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "So incredibly revolting, though, it is to us, and unacceptable, is it just a symptom of the modern times and technology, that actually when it didn't exist, kids would behave in a drunken stupid way in this way and regret it, but they wouldn't all be hauled to court because there would be no evidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I don't think it's just stupid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Do you have any sympathy at all with these two young boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Is it desensitizing them to proper behavior with women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Do you like Dick Cheney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Well, he certainly was very generous with his time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Is he a likeable man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Absolutely, and an engaging man and somebody who is clearly very committed to his point of view and committed to -- I think to the establishment of a legacy that's consistent with his point of view.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Will history judge him in a fairer way, do you think, in centuries to come than perhaps this generation will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, it's hard to know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What was his reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, he has to speak for himself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna Wintour"]}, "docId": "130314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "If I could offer you a chance to take either Anna Wintour or Dick Cheney to a desert island for the rest of your life, which would you take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Well, it's -- that's -- Anna Wintour is a remarkable figure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna Wintour", "Dick Cheney"]}}]